Guide to the Stanford University, Program in Human Biology, Lectures [videorecording]
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Program in Human Biology, lectures [videorecording]
1987-2001
1987-1989
V0246
Stanford University. Program in Human Biology.
13.5 Linear feet 369 videotapes (VHS)
Lectures from classes in the human biology program at Stanford University, 1987-1989, and one tape on "The Human Biology Program at Stanford," 2001. Lecturers include Donald Kennedy, Herant Katchadourian, H. Craig Heller, Jeffrey Wine, Sanford Dornbusch, Sandra Archibald, James Lawry, Roland Ciaranello, Robert Mnookin, Gary Jacobson, Arthur Wolf, John Rick, Frank Stockdale, Dale Kaiser, and Shirley Feldman. Topics include disease, health policy, deviance, cardiovascular system, neurochemistry, human physiology, evolution, genes and genetics, coping with stress, aging, social relations, and family dynamics.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Description of the Collection
Lectures from classes in the human biology program at Stanford University, 1987-1989, and one tape on "The Human Biology Program at Stanford," 2001. Lecturers include Donald Kennedy, Herant Katchadourian, H. Craig Heller, Jeffrey Wine, Sanford Dornbusch, Sandra Archibald, James Lawry, Roland Ciaranello, Robert Mnookin, Gary Jacobson, Arthur Wolf, John Rick, Frank Stockdale, Dale Kaiser, and Shirley Feldman. Topics include disease, health policy, deviance, cardiovascular system, neurochemistry, human physiology, evolution, genes and genetics, coping with stress, aging, social relations, and family dynamics.
Access Terms
Archibald, Sandra Orr.; Archibald, Sandra Orr.; Ciaranello, Roland.; Ciaranello, Roland.; Dornbusch, Sanford M.; Feldman, S. Shirley.; Feldman, S. Shirley.; Heller, H. Craig.; Heller, H. Craig.; Jacobson, Gary C.; Jacobson, Gary C.; Kaiser, Dale.; Kaiser, Dale.; Katchadourian, Herant A.; Kennedy, Donald, 1931-; Lawry, James V., 1940-; Lawry, James V.,, 1940-; Mnookin, Robert H.; Mnookin, Robert H.; Rick, John W.; Rick, John W.; Stanford University. Program in Human Biology.; Stockdale, Frank E.; Stockdale, Frank E.; Wine, Jeffrey.; Wine, Jeffrey.; Wolf, Arthur P.; Wolf, Arthur P.; Biology.; Human physiology.; Videorecordings.
Collection Contents
- Videos
  - Human Biology 131 Great Neglected Diseases. Dr. Toto Olivera: Great Neglected Resources: Killer Snails (Audio Ch. 1 + 2), 5/31/88; V246.1; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 131 Dr. Gary Schoolnik (Audio Ch. 1 + 2), 5/24/88; V246.2; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 131 Great Neglected Diseases. Donald Kennedy Legal Aspects of…? [Faded writing], 5/19/88; V246.3; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 131 Great Neglected Diseases. Dr. Tore Godal "Research Cap. Of Dev. Countries" 1 of 1 (Quad split Aud 1, 2), 4/26/88; V246.4; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 131 Great Neglected Diseases. Ronald Davis "Vaccine Production" 1 of 1 (Quad split audio 1, 2), 4/21/88; V246.5; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 1 Cultural versus Natural Selection, Prof. Durham (Quad Split Audio 1, T. C. 2), 5/18/89; V246.6; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 3A/B Cancer/Black Family: Stockdale/Burton (Quad Split Audio 2 TC 1), 3/15/89; V246.7; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - "The Human Biology Program at Stanford" (TRT: 13:20 Producer: Monica Lam), 2001 Oct 5; V246.8; 1 videotape(s) (DVCAM) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 4A & 4B Spring 1986/87. Donald Kennedy, Human Biology and Health Policy, 6/3/87; V246.9; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 4A & 4B Spring 1986/87. Donald Kennedy, Human Biology and Health Policy, 6/3/87; V246.10; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 4 Spring 1986/87. Herant Katchadourian, Social Deviance, 4/20/87; V246.11; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 4A/4B (Double Lecture) Spring 1986/87. Herant Katchadourian, Homeostasis, Stress, and Adaptation, 4/1/87; V246.12; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 1)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring James Lawry Cardiovascular/Regulation, 5/22, V246.13; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. James Lawry, Cardiovascular/The Vasculature, 5/20/87; V246.14; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller, Regulation of Tb, 5/15/87; V246.15; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller, Respiratory Gas Transport, 5/8/87; V246.16; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller, Respiratory Gas Exchange, 5/6/87; V246.17; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. Richard Thompson, Learning and Memory, 5/4/87; V246.18; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller, Motor Control, 5/1/87; V246.19; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller, CNS & ANS, 4/29/87; V246.20; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller, Neuroendocrine Regulation and Behavior, 4/27/87; V246.21; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller, Hypothalamic/ Pituitary/Gonadal System, 4/24/87; V246.22; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring. Roland Ciaranello, Neurochemistry, Clinical Correlates 4/15, V246.23; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. Jeffrey Wine, Synaptic Transmission, 4/10/87; V246.24; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. Jeffrey Wine The Nerve Impulse, 4/8/87; V246.25; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4A Spring 1986/87. Jeffrey Wine The Transmembrane Potential, 4/6/87; V246.26; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 2)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Sandra Archibald Economic Controls, 5/1/87; V246.27; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Sandra Archibald Economic Controls, 4/29/87; V246.28; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. John Kaplan Legal Control of Crime, 4/22/87; V246.29; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Robert Mnookin Social Control: Law's Response to Divorce, 4/17/87; V246.30; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Shirley Feldman Conflict in the Family: Child Abuse, 4/15/87; V246.31; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring Sanford Dornbusch conflict in the Family: Divorce 4/13, V246.32; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Sanford Dornbusch The Family Unit: Power in the Family, 4/10/87; V246.33; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Herant Katchadourian Ego Defense Mechanisms, 4/8/87; V246.34; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Herant Katchadourian Coping with the Emotional Impact of Disasters, 4/6/87; V246.35; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Herant Katchadourian Coping With Stresses of Adult Life, 4/3/87; V246.36; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller Physiological Systems in Crisis, 6/1/87; V246.37; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Lawrence Crapo Biology of Aging, 5/29/87; V246.38; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller Kidney I, 5/27/87; V246.39; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. H. Craig Heller Kidney II, 5/27/87; V246.40; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 3)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Herant Katchadourian Death and Bereavement, 6/1/87; V246.41; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Herant Katchadourian Psychosocial Aspects of Aging, 5/29/87; V246.42; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. David Maron Prevention of Heart Disease, 5/22/87; V246.43; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. David Maron Risk Factors in Heart Disease, 5/20/87; V246.44; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Terry Karl Managing International Conflicts: The Case of Central America, 5/18/87; V246.45; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Gary Jacobson Controlling Politics, 5/15/87; V246.46; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Gary Jacobson Political Controls; Dilemma of Collective Action, 5/13/87; V246.47; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Sandra Archibald Economic Source of Social Conflict, 5/11/87; V246.48; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Sandra Archibald Economic Controls, 5/8/87; V246.49; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Sandra Archibald Economic Controls, 5/6/87; V246.50; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 4B Spring 1986/87. Sandra Archibald Economic Controls, 5/4/87; V246.51; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 4)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. The Concept of Culture I, Apr 18 1989; V246.52; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. The Concept of Culture II, Apr 20 1989; V246.53; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. William Durham. Mendel's Law and Mitosis, Apr 25 1989; V246.54; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. William Durham. Mendel's Law and Meiosis, Apr 27 1989; V246.55; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. Arthur Wolf, Dale Kaiser. Capacity for Culture/Genetic Code, May 2 1989; V246.56; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. Arthur Wolf, Dale Kaiser. Culture/Protein Synthesis, May 4 1989; V246.57; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. Arthur Wolf, Dale Kaiser. Learning Culture/Protein Synthesis, May 9 1989; V246.58; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. Arthur Wolf, Dale Kaiser. Learning Culture/DNA Replication…, May 11 1989; V246.59; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. William Durham. [untitled], May 18 1989; V246.60; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. Arthur Wolf, William Durham. Prohibition/Genetics of Inbreeding, May 30 1989; V246.61; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 1 Spring 1988/89. Arthur Wolf, William Durham. Child Sex in China/Outbreeding Theory, Jun 1 1989; V246.62; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. H. Craig Heller and Staff. Introduction to Human Biology., Sep 30 1987; V246.63; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Human Diversity: The Lactose Case., Oct 2 1987; V246.64; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Lactose II: Genes and Human Diversity., Oct 5 1987; V246.65; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 5)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Lactose III: Culture and Human Diversity., Oct 7 1987; V246.66; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Evolutionary Theory I: Microevolution., Oct 9 1987; V246.67; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Evolutionary Theory II: Macroevolution., Oct 12 1987; V246.68; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. The Genetics of Inbreeding., Oct 14 1987; V246.69; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Optimal Outbreeding and the Incest Taboo., Oct 16 1987; V246.70; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Childhood Association, Sexual Attraction, and the Incest Taboo., Oct 19 1987; V246.71; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Discussion., Oct 19 1987; V246.72; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Gordon Ringold. Molecular Biology and the Origins of Life: DNA., Oct 21 1987; V246.73; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Gordon Ringold. RNA: Synthesis and Processing., Oct 23 1987; V246.74; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Donald Johnson. The Evolution of Homo., Oct 26 1987; V246.75; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Gordon Ringold. Protein Synthesis., Oct 28 1987; V246.76; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Gordon Ringold. The Evolution of Gene Expression., Oct 30 1987; V246.77; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Gordon Ringold. Regulation of Gene Expression., Nov 2 1987; V246.78; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Gordon Ringold. Manipulation of Gene Expression., Nov 6 1987; V246.79; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 6)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham, Arthur Wolf. Discussion., Nov 9 1987; V246.80; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Evolution: Population Genetics., Nov 11 1987; V246.81; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. The Hardy Weinberg Law., Nov 13 1987; V246.82; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Selection Kinetics I., Nov 16 1987; V246.83; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Selection Kinetics II., Nov 18 1987; V246.84; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Carol Boggs. Ecology: Population Growth., Nov 20 1987; V246.85; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Carol Boggs. Age-Structured Population Growth., Nov 23 1987; V246.86; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Carol Boggs. Population Regulation., Nov 25 1987; V246.87; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Carol Boggs. Competition/Mutualism., Nov 30 1987; V246.88; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Carol Boggs. Predation/Parasitism, Dec 2 1987; V246.89; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Carol Boggs. Community Biology, Dec 4 1987; V246.90; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Craig Heller. Ethology and Animal Behavior, Dec 7 1987; V246.91; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Craig Heller. Sociobiology of Aggression, Dec 9 1987; V246.92; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Human Aggression and Warfare, Dec 11 1987; V246.93; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 7)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Donald Johnson. Human Evolution: The Order of Primates., Sep 30 1988; V246.94; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Donald Johnson. Australopithecines., Oct 3 1988; V246.95; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Evolution and Lactose I., Oct 5 1988; V246.96; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Evolution and Lactose II., Oct 7 1988; V246.97; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Evolution and Lactose III., Oct 10 1988; V246.98; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Evolution: Tempo and Mode (Debate)., Oct 12 1988; V246.99; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Allometry in Evolution: The Brain., Oct 14 1988; V246.100; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham, Arthur Wolf. Imperfections in Evolution/Biology, Culture and Individuals., Oct 17 1988; V246.101; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Neural and Semantic Coding of Color., Oct 19 1988; V246.102; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Genes and Evolution: Case of Sickle Cell., Oct 21 1988; V246.103; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Gordon Ringold. Molecular Biology: DNA., Oct 24 1988; V246.104; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Gordon Ringold. RNA: Synthesis and Processing., Oct 26 1988; V246.105; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Gordon Ringold. Protein Synthesis., Oct 28 1988; V246.106; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Gordon Ringold. Evolution of Gene Expression., Oct 31 1988; V246.107; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 8)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Gordon Ringold. Regulation of Gene Expression., Nov 2 1988; V246.108; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. John Rick. Origins of Complex Societies I., Nov 4 1988; V246.109; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Gordon Ringold. Manipulating Gene Expression/Molecular Evolution., Nov 7 1988; V246.110; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Population Genetics., Nov 9 1988; V246.111; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. The Hardy Weinberg Law., Nov 11 1988; V246.112; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Selection Kinetics I., Nov 14 1988; V246.113; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Selection Kinetics II., Nov 16 1988; V246.114; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. The Demographic Transition., Nov 18 1988; V246.115; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. William Durham. Population and Resources in El Salvador., Nov 21 1988; V246.116; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Population and Resources in China., Nov 23 1988; V246.117; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Carol Boggs. Comm. of Ecology: Comp. and Mutual., Nov 28 1988; V246.118; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Carol Boggs. Predation., Nov 30 1988; V246.119; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Carol Boggs. Diversity of Communities, Dec 2 1988; V246.120; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Carol Boggs. Ecosystem Processes: Hubbard-Brook, Dec 5 1988; V246.121; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 9)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Craig Heller. Sociobiology of Aggression, Dec 7 1988; V246.122; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2A Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Human Aggression: Data from Taiwan, Dec 9 1988; V246.123; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. The Social Construction of Reality., Sep 30 1987; V246.124; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. The Individual and/or Society., Oct 2 1987; V246.125; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Consciousness, False Consciousness, and the Unconscious., Oct 5 1987; V246.126; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Development and Learning., Oct 7 1987; V246.127; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. History and Evolution., Oct 9 1987; V246.128; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Biology, Culture, and Society., Oct 12 1987; V246.129; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Material from H.B. 1., Oct 13 1987; V246.130; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Incest Avoidance and the Incest Taboo., Oct 14 1987; V246.131; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Theories of Incest Prohibition., Oct 16 1987; V246.132; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Childhood Association, Sexual Attraction, and the Incest Taboo., Oct 19 1987; V246.133; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. William Durham, Arthur Wolf. Discussion., Oct 19 1987; V246.134; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Donald Johanson. Human Evolution: The Order Primates., Oct 21 1987; V246.135; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 10)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Donald Johanson. Fossil Primates., Oct 23 1987; V246.136; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Donald Johanson. The Australopithecines., Oct 26 1987; V246.137; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Evolution of the Human Brain., Oct 30 1987; V246.138; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Kirsten Lund, Stewart Patrick (T.A.s). T.A. Panel: Major Models of Human Evolution., Oct 30 1987; V246.139; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Neural and Semantic Coding of Color., Nov 2 1987; V246.140; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Language and Human Evolution., Nov 4 1987; V246.141; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Culture and Color Symbolism., Nov 6 1987; V246.142; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. John Rick. Late Hunter-Gatherers., Nov 11 1987; V246.143; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. John Rick. Origins of Agriculture I., Nov 13 1987; V246.144; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. John Rick. Origins of Agriculture II., Nov 16 1987; V246.145; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. John Rick. Origins of Complex Societies I., Nov 18 1987; V246.146; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. John Rick. Origins of Complex Societies II., Nov 20 1987; V246.147; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. The World at the Dawn of the Modern Era., Nov 23 1987; V246.148; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. The Origins of a World Economy., Nov 25 1987; V246.149; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 11)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. The Demographic Transition., Nov 30 1987; V246.150; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Arthur Wolf. Transformation of the Family, Dec 2 1987; V246.151; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Paul Erlich. Ecosystem Ecology, Dec 4 1987; V246.152; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. Paul Erlich. Extinction, Dec 7 1987; V246.153; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. William Durham. Human Aggression and Warfare, Dec 9 1987; V246.154; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1987/88. William Durham, Craig Heller, Arthur Wolf. Discussion, Dec 11 1987; V246.155; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Craig Heller. On the Origin of Species., Sep 28 1988; V246.156; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Donald Johanson. Fossil Primates., Sep 30 1988; V246.157; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Donald Johanson. The Evolution of Homo., Oct 3 1988; V246.158; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Social Theory: What Is It Good For?, Oct 5 1988; V246.159; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Social Construction of Reality., Oct 7 1988; V246.160; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)
  - Human Biology 2B Fall 1988/89. Arthur Wolf. Consciousness, etc., Oct 10 1988; V246.161; 1 videotape(s) (VHS) (Box 12)